[{"answer": "Yeah, I'll zip in,", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Y'know, I'm better with the mothers than I am with the daughters", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " \"Bailin", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend, you should pay that price", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " What is this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " \"Back o", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, it frees me up. No encumbrances", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "ALL the way, baby", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, no, no, not at all. No, I have always felt that the most important thing in the world is spending time with family", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Very close, yes. Almost painfully close", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh, no no no, I'm fine. Let me help you with these dishes, huh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, I know I don't have to, I want to", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, the that place merger", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How can I go", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No, you'd have to be crazy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yes. Very bad. Very, very bad.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "So lemme get this straigh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Was it in the trash", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Then it was trash", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "But it was in the cylinder", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What's with you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What stone", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I got a stone", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "A kidney stone", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " No, my friend, it was not IN the garbage. It was above the garbage. Hovering. Like an angel. Of course I know your aunt bit it. I kissed her goodbye. Listen, can I tell you something else? In my family, we used to eat out of the garbage all the time.  It was no big thing. That's right. Oh, okay. Bu", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes, good for me", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes, good for me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes, flowers. I will get her flowers, I will go to the florist", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Boy, you can really talk some trash.  I guess that's better than eating it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "All right", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I couldn't believe it. Uh, I mean I thought I was entering a", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well, you know. I mean... I dunno", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yeah, well, y'know what? If I gotta go, and spend time with this girl, then you're coming with me, Dr. my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yeah, well you're going", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Ah, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gymnast.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend, this is my friend", "qsentId": 36}]